{
  "user": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "password": "password",
      "id": 0,
      "voice": 14
    },
    {
      "username": "zac",
      "password": "saban",
      "id": 1,
      "voice": 29
    },
    {
      "username": "aimee",
      "password": "tide",
      "id": 2,
      "voice": 15
    }
  ],
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Animals",
      "description": "Wanna go on a picnic? Alpaca lunch.",
      "shared": false,
      "userID": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Clothes",
      "description": "A lovely deck for learning clothes",
      "shared": true,
      "userID": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "Colors",
      "description": "Aimee's shared deck for learning colors",
      "shared": true,
      "userID": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "name": "Grammar",
      "description": "Zac's deck to be edited and deleted",
      "shared": false,
      "userID": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "Emotions",
      "description": "ðŸ˜€ ðŸ˜‘ ðŸ˜¤ ðŸ™„",
      "shared": true,
      "userID": 0,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "Cheese",
      "description": "Hey Andy",
      "shared": false,
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 8
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "perro",
      "back": "dog",
      "deckID": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "gato",
      "back": "cat",
      "deckID": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "oso",
      "back": "bear",
      "deckID": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "front": "camisa",
      "back": "shirt",
      "deckID": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "front": "pantalones",
      "back": "pants",
      "deckID": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "front": "naranja",
      "back": "orange",
      "deckID": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "negro",
      "back": "black",
      "deckID": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "front": "verde",
      "back": "green",
      "deckID": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "front": "testy boi",
      "back": "another edit",
      "deckID": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "front": "hey zac edit this card",
      "back": "pls",
      "deckID": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "vestido",
      "back": "dress",
      "deckID": 2,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "bufanda",
      "back": "scarf",
      "deckID": 2,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "zapatos",
      "back": "shoes",
      "deckID": 2,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "calcetines",
      "back": "socks",
      "deckID": 2,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "feliz",
      "back": "happy",
      "deckID": 7,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "triste",
      "back": "sad",
      "deckID": 7,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "enojado",
      "back": "angry",
      "deckID": 7,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "emocionado",
      "back": "excited",
      "deckID": 7,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "front": "soprendido",
      "back": "surprise",
      "deckID": 7,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "front": "pÃ¡jaro",
      "back": "bird",
      "deckID": 1,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "front": "mono",
      "back": "monkey",
      "deckID": 1,
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "front": "serpiente",
      "back": "danger noodle",
      "deckID": 1,
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "front": "here is",
      "back": "a card",
      "deckID": 8,
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "front": "tets",
      "back": "edit",
      "deckID": 8,
      "id": 31
    },
    {
      "front": "jirafa",
      "back": "long neck horse",
      "deckID": 1,
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "front": "mapache",
      "back": "racoon",
      "deckID": 1,
      "id": 33
    }
  ],
  "deck_cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "deckID": 1,
      "cardID": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "deckID": 1,
      "cardID": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "deckID": 1,
      "cardID": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "deckID": 2,
      "cardID": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "deckID": 2,
      "cardID": 5
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "deckID": 3,
      "cardID": 6
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "deckID": 3,
      "cardID": 7
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "deckID": 3,
      "cardID": 8
    }
  ]
}